One of these fights was so much lamer with Rogan. We went to a fight on the lawn of you remember this
Which one the fuck it? Oh the playboy man
Man I think that was waddling out was it strike force below that I think it was even worse
Remember the company the Playboy Mansion for a fight. Yeah. Yeah Wow pretty sure it was strike force this old magazine mogul
Look at limps out. It's like five fights in and sits down with these hookers
No, no, no
What's weird is how dated the place was what was it uh?
Strike was right for us. What was weird was how dated the mansion is this like there's an old button phone on the grotto
Like old shit it not just old like everything's just sad John. Well, it's still there in the past
Cosmo's there all day
Everything is like it you know obviously it's all gone now somebody did somebody buy it
Imagine we bought the mansion started doing podcasts out of the
Wait, are we there look at that picture go back up? I think we're right near him behind him perhaps there you are on the right
What a weird
Imagine he died at the right time better than that guy died at the right time huh cuz if he was alive today
Oh my god for him imagine what the me two would have been like for half. There's a documentary about him. It's pretty rough. Yeah
What a good bit about is uh the mansion for sale?
Find out the Playboy Manchester
They saw the mansion is the magazine even going why would it's like if you go to